<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8"?>
<component type="desktop">
  <id>stellarium.desktop</id>
  <metadata_license>CC0-1.0</metadata_license>
  <project_license>GPL-2.0+</project_license>
  <name>Stellarium</name>
  <name xml:lang="af">Stellarium</name>
  <name xml:lang="an">Stellarium</name>
  <name xml:lang="ast">Stellarium</name>
  <name xml:lang="be">Stellarium</name>
  <name xml:lang="bg">Stellarium</name>
  <name xml:lang="br">Stellarium</name>
  <name xml:lang="bs">Stellarium</name>
  <name xml:lang="ca">Stellarium</name>
  <name xml:lang="cs">Stellarium</name>
  <name xml:lang="csb">Stellarium</name>
  <name xml:lang="cy">Stellarium</name>
  <name xml:lang="da">Stellarium</name>
  <name xml:lang="de">Stellarium</name>
  <name xml:lang="el">Stellarium</name>
  <name xml:lang="en-CA">Stellarium</name>
  <name xml:lang="en-GB">Stellarium</name>
  <name xml:lang="eo">Stellarium</name>
  <name xml:lang="es">Stellarium</name>
  <name xml:lang="et">Stellarium</name>
  <name xml:lang="eu">Stellarium</name>
  <name xml:lang="fa">Stellarium</name>
  <name xml:lang="fi">Stellarium</name>
  <name xml:lang="fr">Stellarium</name>
  <name xml:lang="ga">Stellarium</name>
  <name xml:lang="gd">Stellarium</name>
  <name xml:lang="gl">Stellarium</name>
  <name xml:lang="gu">Stellarium</name>
  <name xml:lang="he">Stellarium</name>
  <name xml:lang="hi">स्टेलेरियम</name>
  <name xml:lang="hne">Stellarium</name>
  <name xml:lang="hr">Stellarium</name>
  <name xml:lang="hu">Stellarium</name>
  <name xml:lang="hy">Stellarium</name>
  <name xml:lang="id">Stellarium</name>
  <name xml:lang="is">Stellarium</name>
  <name xml:lang="it">Stellarium</name>
  <name xml:lang="ja">Stellarium</name>
  <name xml:lang="jv">Stellarium</name>
  <name xml:lang="ka">Stellarium</name>
  <name xml:lang="kk">Stellarium</name>
  <name xml:lang="km">Stellarium</name>
  <name xml:lang="ko">스텔라리움</name>
  <name xml:lang="ky">Stellarium</name>
  <name xml:lang="la">Stellarium</name>
  <name xml:lang="lb">Stellarium</name>
  <name xml:lang="lt">Stellarium</name>
  <name xml:lang="lv">Stellarium</name>
  <name xml:lang="mai">Stellarium</name>
  <name xml:lang="mk">Stellarium</name>
  <name xml:lang="ml">Stellarium</name>
  <name xml:lang="ms">Stellarium</name>
  <name xml:lang="nb">Stellarium</name>
  <name xml:lang="nds">Stellarium</name>
  <name xml:lang="ne">Stellarium</name>
  <name xml:lang="nl">Stellarium</name>
  <name xml:lang="nn">Stellarium</name>
  <name xml:lang="oc">Stellarium</name>
  <name xml:lang="pa">Stellarium</name>
  <name xml:lang="pl">Stellarium</name>
  <name xml:lang="pt">Stellarium</name>
  <name xml:lang="pt-BR">Stellarium</name>
  <name xml:lang="ro">Stellarium</name>
  <name xml:lang="ru">Stellarium</name>
  <name xml:lang="sah">Stellarium</name>
  <name xml:lang="se">Stellarium</name>
  <name xml:lang="si">Stellarium</name>
  <name xml:lang="sk">Stellarium</name>
  <name xml:lang="sl">Stellarium</name>
  <name xml:lang="sq">Stellarium</name>
  <name xml:lang="sr">Стеларијум</name>
  <name xml:lang="sv">Stellarium</name>
  <name xml:lang="ta">Stellarium</name>
  <name xml:lang="te">స్టెల్లారియమ్</name>
  <name xml:lang="tg">Stellarium</name>
  <name xml:lang="th">Stellarium</name>
  <name xml:lang="tr">Stellarium</name>
  <name xml:lang="tt">Stellarium</name>
  <name xml:lang="ug">Stellarium</name>
  <name xml:lang="uk">Stellarium</name>
  <name xml:lang="vi">Stellarium</name>
  <name xml:lang="xh">Stellarium</name>
  <name xml:lang="zh-CN">Stellarium</name>
  <name xml:lang="zh-HK">Stellarium</name>
  <name xml:lang="zh-TW">Stellarium</name>
  <summary>Desktop Planetarium</summary>
  <summary xml:lang="af">Werkskerm Planetarium</summary>
  <summary xml:lang="ast">Planetariu pal escritoriu</summary>
  <summary xml:lang="be">Настольны планетарыум</summary>
  <summary xml:lang="bg">Настолен планетаруим</summary>
  <summary xml:lang="br">Planetarium a vurev</summary>
  <summary xml:lang="bs">Stoni planetarij</summary>
  <summary xml:lang="ca">Planetari per a l'escriptori</summary>
  <summary xml:lang="cs">Planetárium na vaší obrazovce</summary>
  <summary xml:lang="csb">Planetarium na pùlce</summary>
  <summary xml:lang="cy">Planetariwm Penbwrdd</summary>
  <summary xml:lang="da">Planetarieprogram</summary>
  <summary xml:lang="de">Das Planetarium für den Schreibtisch</summary>
  <summary xml:lang="el">Επιτραπέζιο πλανητάριο</summary>
  <summary xml:lang="en-CA">Desktop Planetarium</summary>
  <summary xml:lang="en-GB">Desktop Planetarium</summary>
  <summary xml:lang="eo">Tabula planetario</summary>
  <summary xml:lang="es">Planetario de escritorio</summary>
  <summary xml:lang="et">Töölaua planetaarium</summary>
  <summary xml:lang="eu">Mahaigaineko planetarioa</summary>
  <summary xml:lang="fa">آسمان‌نمای رومیزی</summary>
  <summary xml:lang="fi">Työpöytäplanetaario</summary>
  <summary xml:lang="fr">Planétarium virtuel</summary>
  <summary xml:lang="ga">Pláinéadlann Deisce</summary>
  <summary xml:lang="gd">Planaideach Bàrr-deasc</summary>
  <summary xml:lang="gl">Planetario de escritorio</summary>
  <summary xml:lang="gu">ડેસ્કટોપ પર પ્લેનેટેરીયમ</summary>
  <summary xml:lang="he">פלנטריום שולחני</summary>
  <summary xml:lang="hi">डेस्कटॉप प्लेनेटेरियम</summary>
  <summary xml:lang="hne">डेस्कटाप प्लेनेटेरियम</summary>
  <summary xml:lang="hr">Planetarij radne površine</summary>
  <summary xml:lang="hu">Planetárium a munkaasztalon</summary>
  <summary xml:lang="is">Skjáborðsstjörnuver</summary>
  <summary xml:lang="it">Planetario per il desktop</summary>
  <summary xml:lang="ja">デスクトップ・プラネタリウム</summary>
  <summary xml:lang="ka">სამაგიდო პლანეტარიუმი</summary>
  <summary xml:lang="kk">Экрандағы планетарий</summary>
  <summary xml:lang="km">សំណាក​ចក្រវាល​ផ្ទៃតុ</summary>
  <summary xml:lang="ko">데스크톱 플레네타리움(별자리투영)</summary>
  <summary xml:lang="ky">Үстөлдүк планетарий</summary>
  <summary xml:lang="lt">Virtualus Planetariumas</summary>
  <summary xml:lang="lv">Darbvirsmas Planetārijs</summary>
  <summary xml:lang="mai">डेस्कटाप प्लेनेटेरियम</summary>
  <summary xml:lang="mk">Планетариум на работна површина</summary>
  <summary xml:lang="ml">പണിയിട പ്ലാനറ്റേറിയം</summary>
  <summary xml:lang="ms">Planetarium atas meja</summary>
  <summary xml:lang="nb">Planetarium for skrivebordet</summary>
  <summary xml:lang="nds">Planetarium för den Schriefdisch</summary>
  <summary xml:lang="ne">डेस्कटप ग्रहमण्डल</summary>
  <summary xml:lang="nl">Planetarium op uw bureaublad</summary>
  <summary xml:lang="nn">Skrivebordsplanetarium</summary>
  <summary xml:lang="oc">Planetari de burèu</summary>
  <summary xml:lang="pa">ਡੈਸਕਟਾਪ ਪਲੇਟੇਰੀਅਮ</summary>
  <summary xml:lang="pl">Podręczne planetarium</summary>
  <summary xml:lang="pt">Planetário de Ambiente de Trabalho</summary>
  <summary xml:lang="pt-BR">Planetário para computador</summary>
  <summary xml:lang="ro">Planetariu de birou</summary>
  <summary xml:lang="ru">Настольный планетарий</summary>
  <summary xml:lang="se">Čállenbeavdeplánetaria</summary>
  <summary xml:lang="sk">Planetárium vašej plochy</summary>
  <summary xml:lang="sl">Namizni planetarij</summary>
  <summary xml:lang="sr">Планетаријум на радној површини</summary>
  <summary xml:lang="sv">Skrivbordsplanetarium</summary>
  <summary xml:lang="ta">பணிமேடை கோளரங்கம்</summary>
  <summary xml:lang="tg">Планетарии рӯимизӣ</summary>
  <summary xml:lang="th">ท้องฟ้าจำลองบนคอมพิวเตอร์แบบตั้งโต๊ะ</summary>
  <summary xml:lang="tr">Masaüstündeki Samanyolu Sistemi</summary>
  <summary xml:lang="ug">ئۈستەلئۈستى رەسەتخانىسى</summary>
  <summary xml:lang="uk">Настільний планетарій</summary>
  <summary xml:lang="vi">Ngắm sao trên màn hình máy tính</summary>
  <summary xml:lang="xh">Indlu ye Desktop</summary>
  <summary xml:lang="zh-CN">桌面天文馆</summary>
  <summary xml:lang="zh-HK">桌面星象儀</summary>
  <summary xml:lang="zh-TW">桌面天文圖</summary>
  <description>
    <p>Stellarium renders 3D photo-realistic skies in real time with OpenGL. It displays stars, constellations, planets and nebulae, and has many other features including multiple panoramic landscapes, fog, light pollution simulation and a built-in scripting engine.</p>
    <p xml:lang="de">Stellarium bietet eine photorealistische Himmelsdarstellung mit OpenGL. Es zeigt Sterne, Sternbilder, Planeten und nebelartige Objekte und hat viele andere Funktionen, u.a. austauschbare Landschaftspanoramen incl. Bodennebel und Beleuchtungssimulation, und eine eingebaute Script-Funktion.</p>
    <p xml:lang="en-CA">Stellarium renders 3D photo-realistic skies in real time with OpenGL. It displays stars, constellations, planets and nebulae, and has many other features including multiple panoramic landscapes, fog, light pollution simulation and a built-in scripting engine.</p>
    <p xml:lang="en-GB">Stellarium renders 3D photo-realistic skies in real time with OpenGL. It displays stars, constellations, planets and nebulae, and has many other features including multiple panoramic landscapes, fog, light pollution simulation and a built-in scripting engine.</p>
    <p xml:lang="es">Stellarium traza cielos 3D fotorealísticos en tiempo real con OpenGL. Muestra estrellas, constelaciones, planetas y nebulosas, y tiene muchas otras características incluyendo múltiples paisajes panorámicos, neblina, simulación de contaminación lumínica y un motor de secuencias de órdenes integrado.</p>
    <p xml:lang="fr">Stellarium présente le ciel en temps réel et en 3D de manière photoréaliste au moyen de OpenGL. Il permet d'afficher les étoiles, les constellations, les planètes et les nébuleuses. De nombreuses autres fonctionnalités sont disponibles, parmi lesquels l'utilisation de nombreux paysages panoramiques, la simulation du brouillard et de la pollution lumineuse. Un moteur de scripts est également proposé.</p>
    <p xml:lang="gl">Stellarium ofrece ceos foto-realistas 3D en tempo real con OpenGL. Amosa estrelas, constelacións, planetas e nebulosas e ten moitos outros recursos, incluíndo múltiples paisaxes panorámicas, néboa, simulación de contaminación lumínica e un mecanismo de script incorporado.</p>
    <p xml:lang="it">Stellarium renderizza i cieli in realtà fotografica 3D in tempo reale usando OpenGL. Mostra stelle, costellazioni, pianeti e nebulose, e possiede molte altre caratteristiche compresi paesaggi panoramici multipli, nebbia, simulazione dell'inquinamento luminoso e un motore di scripting built-in.</p>
    <p xml:lang="lt">Stellarium atvaizduoja trimatį realistišką dangaus vaizdą realaus laiko režime, naudodamas OpenGL. Jis atvaizduoja žvaigždes, žvaigždynus, planetas ir ūkus, ir turi daugelį kitų funkcijų, tokių kaip panoraminiai kraštovaizdžiai, rūko bei šviesos taršos modeliavimas ir integruotas scenarijų variklis.</p>
    <p xml:lang="pt-BR">O Stellarium renderiza um céu fotorrealístico tridimensional em tempo real com o OpenGL. Ele mostra estrelas, constelações, planetas e nebulosoas e possui vários outros recursos, incluindo paisagens panorâmicas múltiplas, nevoeiro, simulação da poluição luminosa e um mecanismo de apresentações embutido.</p>
    <p xml:lang="ru">Stellarium рисует трехмерное фотореалистичное небо в режиме реального времени с OpenGL. Он отображает звезды, созвездия, планеты и туманности, и имеет много других функций, включая несколько панорамных пейзажей, туман, моделирование засветки и встроенный движок сценариев.</p>
    <p xml:lang="sv">Stellarium renderar fotorealistiska 3D-himlar i realtid med OpenGL. Det visar stjärnor, stjärnbilder, planeter och nebulosor, och har många andra funktioner inklusive flera panoramalandskap, dimma, simulering av ljusförorening och en inbyggd skriptmotor.</p>
    <p xml:lang="th">Stellarium แสดงท้องฟ้าเสมือนจริงแบบ 3 มิติ ตามเวลาจริงด้วย OpenGL สามารถแสดงดาวฤกษ์ กลุ่มดาว ดาวเคราะห์ และเนบิวลา มีคุณลักษณะอื่น ๆ อีกมากมาย รวมทั้งการจำลองภูมิทัศน์รอบตัวในแบบต่าง ๆ หมอก จำลองผลจากมลพิษทางแสง และมีระบบการประมวลผลสคริปต์ในตัว</p>
    <p xml:lang="uk">Stellarium відтворює просторову фотореалістичну картину зоряного неба у режимі реального часу за допомогою OpenGL. Програма здатна показувати зірки, сузір’я, планети і туманності. Має безліч інших можливостей, зокрема показ декількох панорамних ландшафтів, туману, імітацію світлового забруднення та вбудований рушій керування за допомогою сценаріїв.</p>
    <p>Stellarium comes with a star catalogue of about 600 thousand stars and it is possible to download extra catalogues with up to 210 million stars.</p>
    <p xml:lang="de">Stellarium kommt mit einem Sternkatalog von etwa 600.000 Sternen, und es ist möglich, weitere Kataloge mit bis zu 210 Mio Sternen herunterzuladen.</p>
    <p xml:lang="en-CA">Stellarium comes with a star catalogue of about 600 thousand stars and it is possible to download extra catalogues with up to 210 million stars.</p>
    <p xml:lang="en-GB">Stellarium comes with a star catalogue of about 600 thousand stars and it is possible to download extra catalogues with up to 210 million stars.</p>
    <p xml:lang="es">Stellarium viene con un catálogo cerca de 600 mil estrellas y es posible descargar catálogos extra con hasta 210 millones de estrellas.</p>
    <p xml:lang="fr">Stellarium est livré avec un catalogue d'environ 600 mille étoiles. Des catalogues supplémentaires comportant jusqu'à 210 millions d'étoiles peuvent être téléchargés gratuitement.</p>
    <p xml:lang="gl">Stellarium vén cun catálogo de estrelas de preto de 600 mil estrelas e é posible facer a descarga de catálogos extra con ata 210 millóns de estrelas.</p>
    <p xml:lang="it">Stellarium viene fornito con un catalogo di circa 600.000 stelle ed è possibile scaricare cataloghi extra fino a 210 milioni di stelle.</p>
    <p xml:lang="lt">Stellarium platinamas su maždaug 600 tūkstančių žvaigždžių katalogu. Galima atsisiųsti papildomus katalogus ir padidinti atvaizduojamų žvaigždžių skaičių iki 210 milijonų.</p>
    <p xml:lang="pt-BR">O Stellarium vem com um catálogo estelar com cerca de 600.000 estrelas, e é possível baixar catálogos adicionais com até 210 milhões de estrelas.</p>
    <p xml:lang="ru">Stellarium поставляется со звездным каталога на примерно 600 тысяч звезд и можно скачать дополнительные каталоги и расширить число звёзд до 210 миллионов.</p>
    <p xml:lang="sv">Stellarium kommer med en stjärnkatalog med ungefär 600000 stjärnor och det är möjligt att hämta hem extra kataloger med upp till 210 miljoner stjärnor.</p>
    <p xml:lang="th">Stellarium แสดงดาวฤกษ์จากบัญชีดาวที่มีดาวอยู่ประมาณ 600,000 ดวง และยังสามารถดาวน์โหลดเพิ่มเติมให้มีดาวฤกษ์ได้ถึง 210 ล้านดวง</p>
    <p xml:lang="uk">До пакунка Stellarium включено зоряний каталог, у якому близько 600 тисяч записів зірок. Ви також можете отримати з інтернету додаткові каталоги, у яких до 210 мільйонів записів.</p>
    <p>Stellarium has multiple sky cultures - see the constellations from the traditions of Polynesian, Inuit, Navajo, Korean, Lakota, Egyptian and Chinese astronomers, as well as the traditional Western constellations.</p>
    <p xml:lang="de">Stellarium hat vielfältige mythologische Figuren, etwa die Sternbilder der Polynesier, Inuit, Navajo, Lakota, Koreaner, Ägypter und Chinesischer Astronomen, neben den bekannten Westlichen.</p>
    <p xml:lang="en-CA">Stellarium has multiple sky cultures - see the constellations from the traditions of Polynesian, Inuit, Navajo, Korean, Lakota, Egyptian and Chinese astronomers, as well as the traditional Western constellations.</p>
    <p xml:lang="en-GB">Stellarium has multiple sky cultures - see the constellations from the traditions of Polynesian, Inuit, Navajo, Korean, Lakota, Egyptian and Chinese astronomers, as well as the traditional Western constellations.</p>
    <p xml:lang="es">Stellarium tiene múltiples culturas estelares - véa las constelaciones desde las tradiciones de astrónomos de Polinesia, Inuit, Navajo, Coreana, Lakota, Egipcias, así como las tradicionales constelaciones Occidentales.</p>
    <p xml:lang="fr">Stellarium propose l'affichage de constellations de plusieurs cultures, issues des traditions d'astronomes de Polynésie, Inuit, Navajo, de Corée, Lakota, d'Égypte et de Chine, ainsi que les constellations traditionnelle de la culture occidentale.</p>
    <p xml:lang="gl">Stellarium ten ceos de múltiples culturas - amosa as constelacións das tradicións dos astrónomos polinesios, Inuit, Navajos, coreanos, Lakotas, exipcios e chineses, así como as constelacións occidentais tradicionais.</p>
    <p xml:lang="it">Stellarium include molteplici culture del cielo: osserva le costellazioni dalle tradizioni degli astronomi polinesiani, Inuit, Navajo, coreani, Lakota, egizi e cinesi, oltre alle tradizionali costellazioni della cultura occidentale.</p>
    <p xml:lang="lt">Stellarium turi daugybę žvaigždynų piešinių - pamatykite tradicinius Polinezijos, Inuitų, Navaho, Korėjos, Lakotos, Egipto ir Kinijos žvaigždynus, o taip pat ir tradicinius vakarietiškus.</p>
    <p xml:lang="pt-BR">O Stellarium tem diversas culturas estelares: veja as constelações a partir das tradições de astrônomos polinésios, inuítes, navajos, coreanos, lacotas, egípcios e chineses, bem como as constelações ocidentais tradicionais.</p>
    <p xml:lang="ru">Stellarium имеет множество культур небо - посмотрите традиционные созвездия для полинезийцев, инуитов, навахо, корейцев, лакота, египетских и китайских астрономов, а также традиционные западные созвездия.</p>
    <p xml:lang="sv">Stellarium har flera stjärnmytologier - se stjärnbilderna enligt traditionerna hos polynesiska, inuitiska, navajoiska, koreanska, lakotaiska, egyptiska och kinesiska astronomer, så väl som de traditionella västerländska stjärnbilderna.</p>
    <p xml:lang="uk">У Stellarium передбачено можливість спостерігати за декількома картинами зоряного неба: ви можете побачити його таким, яким його собі уявляли полінезійці, інуїти, навахо, корейці, лакота, єгиптяни та китайці, а також ознайомитися із традиційними західноєвропейськими сузір’ями.</p>
    <p>It is also possible to visit other planets in the solar system - see what the sky looked like to the Apollo astronauts, or what the rings of Saturn looks like from Titan.</p>
    <p xml:lang="de">Man kann auch andere Planeten unseres Sonnensystems besuchen - erleben Sie den Himmelsanblick der Apollo-Astronauten, oder wie sich Saturn von seinem Mond Titan aus zeigt.</p>
    <p xml:lang="en-CA">It is also possible to visit other planets in the solar system - see what the sky looked like to the Apollo astronauts, or what the rings of Saturn looks like from Titan.</p>
    <p xml:lang="en-GB">It is also possible to visit other planets in the solar system - see what the sky looked like to the Apollo astronauts, or what the rings of Saturn looks like from Titan.</p>
    <p xml:lang="es">También es posible visitar otros planetas en el sistema solar - ver como veían el cielo los astronautas de Apollo, o como se ven los anillos de Saturno desde Titán.</p>
    <p xml:lang="fr">Il est également possible de visiter d'autres corps célestes du système solaire, par exemple pour voir le ciel comme les astronautes du programme Apollo ou observer les anneaux de Saturne depuis Titan.</p>
    <p xml:lang="gl">Tamén é posible visitar outros planetas no sistema solar - ver o ceo coma os astronautas do Apollo, ou os aneis de Saturno dende Titan.</p>
    <p xml:lang="it">È anche possibile visitare altri pianeti nel Sistema Solare: guarda come appariva il cielo agli astronauti delle missioni Apollo, o come appaiono gli anelli di Saturno da Titano.</p>
    <p xml:lang="lt">Taip pat galima apsilankyti kitose Saulės sistemos planetose - pamatykite, kaip dangus atrodė Apollo astronautams, arba kaip Saturno žiedai atrodo iš Titano.</p>
    <p xml:lang="pt-BR">Também é possível visitar outros planetas no sistema solar: veja como o céu pareceu para os astronautas da Apollo ou como os anéis de Saturno parecem a partir de Titã.</p>
    <p xml:lang="ru">Кроме того, можно посетить другие планеты в Солнечной системе - посмотрите на что было похоже небо на месте посадки астронавтов Аполлона, или как выглядят кольца Сатурна с Титана.</p>
    <p xml:lang="sv">Det är också möjligt att besöka andra planeter i solsystemet - se hur himlen såg ut för astronauterna på Apollo, eller hur Saturnus ringar ser ut från Titan.</p>
    <p xml:lang="th">เราสามารถย้ายไปอยู่บนดาวเคราะห์ดวงอื่นในระบบสุริยะ เพื่อดูว่าท้องฟ้าเป็นอย่างไรในมุมมองของนักบินอวกาศในโครงการอะพอลโล หรือวงแหวนของดาวเสาร์มีลักษณะอย่างไรเมื่อมองจากดาวบริวารไททัน</p>
    <p xml:lang="uk">Також передбачено можливість «відвідання» інших планет Сонячної системи: ви зможете спостерігати небо таким, яким його бачили астронавти «Аполлонів», або побачити кільця Сатурна з Титана.</p>
  </description>
  <url type="homepage">http://www.stellarium.org/</url>
  <url type="bugtracker">https://bugs.launchpad.net/stellarium</url>
  <url type="help">http://www.stellarium.org/wiki/index.php/Stellarium_User_Guide</url>
  <screenshots>
    <screenshot type="default">
      <image>http://www.stellarium.org/img/screenshots/0.10-constellation-art-on.jpg</image>
    </screenshot>
  </screenshots>
  <provides>
    <binary>stellarium</binary>
  </provides>
</component>
